var questions = [
{
    "question": "La casa de Papel is a series produced by:",
    "option1": "Sergio Marquina",
    "option2": "Stéphane Giusti",
    "option3": "Alex Pina",
    "option4": "Ricardo Ramos",
    "answer": "3"
},

{
    "question": "When was the Casa de papel series first broadcast?",
    "option1": "17th january 2015",
    "option2": "6th november 2016",
    "option3": "21th december 2018",
    "option4": "2th may 2017",
    "answer": "4"
},

{
    "question": "The song Bella cio is at the origin:",
     "option1": "an Italian revolutionary song",
     "option2": "a revolutionary Spanish song",
     "option3": "a patriotic Portuguese song",
     "option4": "a foreign patriotic song",
     "answer": "1"
},

{
    "question": "The purpose of the tape is to print:",
     "option1": "2.4 million euros in denomination of 100 euros",
     "option2": "2.4 billion euros in denominations of 50 euros",
     "option3": "1 million euro in denomination of 50 euros",
     "option4": "10 million euros in denominations of 100 euros",
     "answer": "2"
},

{
    "question": "What does the professor say at the end of season 3?",
     "option1": "We are at War!",
     "option2": "This is a flight",
     "option3": "We are not going to destroy the system but threaten it",
     "option4": "We want peace!",
     "answer": "1"
},

{
    "question": "What important role does Nairobi play in the series?",
     "option1": "She takes care of the hostages",
     "option2": "She takes care of the tickets",
     "option3": "She takes care of the proper functioning of the weapons",
     "option4": "She takes care of her brother",
     "answer": "2"
},

{
    "question": "Check the true answer about Stockholm:",
     "option1": "His real name is Raquel",
     "option2": "She has a daughter",
     "option3": "She has a relationship with Denver",
     "option4": "She is the bank manager",
     "answer": "3"
},

{
    "question": "Which of these statements about Palermo is false?",
     "option1": "He is above all a feminist",
     "option2": "His real name is Martin",
     "option3": "he has the role of team leader",
     "option4": "Palermo had a hidden love for Berlin",
     "answer": "1"
},

{
    "question": "Denver is the son of ...",
     "option1": "Bogota",
     "option2": "Moscow",
     "option3": "Berlin",
     "option4": "Helsinki",
     "answer": "2"
},

{
    "question": "Which of the following statements is false about the professor:",
     "option1": "He's an impatient man",
     "option2": "He planned the turning down to the smallest detail",
     "option3": "He intends to leave with more than 2 billion euros from the bank",
     "option4": "a real ghost in the eyes of the authorities",
     "answer": "1"
},


{
    "question": "The idea of the robbery is not that of the Professor but that ...",
     "option1": "from Rio",
     "option2": "from Tokyo",
     "option3": "from her half-brother Berlin",
     "option4": "from the professor's father",
     "answer": "4"
},

{
    "question": "Originally, Helsinki is:",
     "option1": "a thief",
     "option2": "a computer genius",
     "option3": "a soldier",
     "option4": "a burglar",
     "answer": "3"
},

{
    "question": "What is Bogota's job?",
     "option1": "he is a welder",
     "option2": "he is a police officer",
     "option3": "he is a thief",
     "option4": "he is on the run",
     "answer": "1"
},

{
    "question": "Marseille comes from ...",
     "option1": "Marseille",
     "option2": "Paris",
     "option3": "Nantes",
     "option4": "we don't know",
     "answer": "4"
},

{
    "question": "Check the false statement about Rio",
     "option1": "it's a hacker",
     "option2": "his real name is ricardo",
     "option3": "it is wanted for numerous hacks",
     "option4": "he is in love with Tokyo",
     "answer": "2"
},

{
    "question": "Tokyo is:",
     "option1": "searched for theft",
     "option2": "actually Monica",
     "option3": "the narrator of the story",
     "option4": "at the origin of the turning",
     "answer": "3"
},

{
    "question": "So, did the site convince you ?",
     "option1": "Yess !!!",
     "option2": "Yess i will watch casa de papel now",
     "option3": "Yes of course",
     "option4": "maybe yes maybe not",
     "answer": "2"
},


]